Breakthrough!
I can hear breakthrough!
My business, breakthrough!
My family, breakthrough!
My finances, career, destiny, health, country, nation - breakthrough!
No breakthrough!
This one says, "No breakthrough".
I block them!
Do you agree with him?
No!
This is to tell you that there is breakthrough.
Indeed, satan is powerless in the face of God's armour.
This man begins to feel uncomfortable as the fire of the Holy Ghost consumes the evil spirit in him.
Do the sign you do now.
No breakthrough, I block them.
You say what?
I blocked all the blessings.
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
Hallelujah!
Look - this is a sign that we are getting there.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Hallelujah!
Amen.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
If you are praying and one of them comes out to say, "No breakthrough",
that means that, they are the ones that are giving you this trouble that you are carrying.
If the message touched them that you have been released,
they have to fight back.
Say, "I have been released!"
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
If Jesus releases you, you are released perpetually!
Who are you?
I am Lakozi, the lord of darkness.
The wise men will deliver him.
DELIVERANCE TIME
Wiseman Daniel moves throughout the congregation.
Being used by God Almighty as a channel of healing and deliverance in Jesus' name.
As Wiseman Daniel moves, the power of God comes on the scene and uproots whatever
that had not been planted by God in the lives of the people.
Remember, demons are the cause of the enormous growth of pain, bitterness, disappointment,
sickness, that is going on around the world today.
Look at this man.
Upon touching him, the evil spirit that possessed him is arrested by the fire of the Holy Ghost,
and he becomes very uncomfortable.
Let's see how he was delivered in Jesus' name.
All over your body - fire, in the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
You wicked spirit. Come here!
Fire!
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Fire, in the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
All over your body - fire!
Come here and talk!
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Who are you? Speak out!
I am the spirit of lies.
How many of you are in this body?
We are many.
Who is the first person?
Lies.
Second?
Destroyer.
Third?
Killer.
Fourth?
Stealing.
Fifth?
Disturbance.
What have you all done to this body?
We are killing, destroying him. We don't want him here.
You do not want him here?
Yes.
How far have you gone in destroying him?
We have put cancer in his body and it is eating him.
What else have you done to him?
We have destroyed his spirit, he doesn't have love, only anger and hatred.
What does this man do for a living?
He is a hydraulic filter engineer
and he was a minister of us, the USL.
What things have you done to the career of this man?
We have destroyed him.
How?
Stealing at work, instigating fights at work.
What else have you done to him?
We have made him to rape, sodomize, as he was sodomized.
What happened to him afterwards?
Afterwards, he was trained to be the USL leader - the United Satanic Leaders in South Africa.
As the head of this occultic background, what are the things you have done to him?
We have done many things and sent him to do many things.
What are the things you've sent him to do? What is his mission on this earth?
His mission is to destroy all the churches of God - the living churches.
His mission is to destroy all churches of God?
Yes!
The living churches?
Yes.
How possible is that?
It is possible.
How?
By confusing all the members of the churches.
How far have you gone in doing that?
Spreading the Word of God in a wrong way.
Spreading the Word of God in a wrong way - how?
By telling the children of God that God is the God who supplies and loves
but not the way they think and not the way the pastors are preaching.
How do you manipulate them?
We use our holy communion.
You use your holy communion?
Yes.
Your own holy communion?
What is the difference of your holy communion and the right one?
The difference is that in our holy communion,
we buy the juice, the red wine and take our blood and mix with it.
Then, we let them drink it.
What would happen to their spiritual lives?
Before we mix it, we pray for our blood.
We call on all demons to enter.
When they drink, they become demon-possessed.
They become demon-possessed?
Yes.
How many have you initiated through these means?
Many in South Africa.
We have finished churches.
We don’t want you. We don’t want T.B. Joshua.
You say you destroyed churches.
Yes.
Can you enter any living church that has the Spirit of God?
Every living church like this one.
Because this church has raised true leaders as they are the appointed right ones
of Jehovah God and we are against that.
You are against that?
We are against that.
What is your mission here?
My mission here ... I didn’t want my son to come here. This one you are talking to.
I wanted him to stay back and your prophet, father, the right appointed one,
prayed against our plans.
We were supposed to destroy South Africa on the 16th and 17th.
Again, your father destroyed our plans.
What were the plans you intended to execute that my mentor, Prophet T.B. Joshua, has destroyed?
This young man was not supposed to come here.
We had planned with our police – the SAPS group.
We had planned to stop him at the airport but he escaped.
You said you do not want my mentor, Prophet T.B. Joshua, to get into South Africa.
Yes.
Why?
What has he done to you?
Why do you not want him to go to South Africa?
We don’t want him to come to South Africa because he will reveal the truth of the true church.
Is that why you do not want him to go to South Africa?
Yes, because he is going to destroy our evangelists, prophets and pastors.
Does it mean that you have people you call prophets and evangelists?
Yes, we’ve got our own who inject their blood into the wine for our holy communion.
You have people that disguise to be pastors, prophets, evangelists?
Yes.
What is the difference between them and true prophets?
The true prophets act on the Word,
and by acting on the Word they are activating the power of the Word in them.
What about the ones you are using? From your demonic kingdom?
The false prophets, they preach only; they don’t act on the Word.
Now that you here - what do you want to do now?
Now, we have planned to confuse the church, to spread the spirit of confusion,
for the church to doubt their blessings.
What is the trouble a living church is causing to your demonic kingdom?
A living church causes big problems to our kingdom.
What kind of problem?
The water that the Prophet is using is like floods of water coming into our kingdom
and destroying our connections.
Now you are talking about this?
It is fire; it is killing my eyes.
It is doing what?
It is killing my eyes.
But this is ordinary water.
Floods of fire.
What is the difference between this and ordinary water?
It is a big difference because this one has been touched from Heaven.
So right now, you wicked spirit - it is time you leave this body.
Fire, in the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Come here!
All over your body - fire! Fire, in the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Out! Out, in the mighty name of Jesus Christ! Out!
You demon - out!
In Jesus' name!
Set Free in Jesus' Name
Thank you, Jesus.
How are you, sir?
I am fine.
Do you remember what happened to you?
Thank you, Jesus.
That very demon that has tormented you and your career is out.
Give thanks to God. You are free!
Thank You, Jesus! Thank You, God!
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
Testimony Time
As we know, there are many many valuable lessons, that we are going to learn from our brother's experience,
and many important insights into the spiritual world, so we as Christians can be fully equipped
to stand firm and strong in our relationship with God.
So, once again - viewers all around the world, brothers and sisters in Christ here - let us listen carefully
to our brother and open our hearts as we receive the message of God through his words.
So brother, you are welcome. Can you first introduce yourself to us?
Tell us your name and where are you from.
Emmanuel! (God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Lawrence Moala from South Africa.
I am happy to be here.
I was in a satanic occult.
I was initiated into the occult when I was 11 years old, in 1988.
I grew up in the occult.
The only thing I knew was what I was taught being raised in an occult.
I was initiated by one of the elders in the family.
I remember there was one day, he took me to a mountain in South Africa.
According to our tradition, young men at the early age of 11 years and older
are taken to the mountain to be made men.
He told me that he was taking me there to make me a true man.
I went there, thinking that I was going to be a true man but
when we went into the mountain, it was no longer that.
He sodomised me there as part of the occult initiation.
From there, he told me, “You must not be worried because on the third day,
you must come back here and I will introduce you to the king of the occult
which is the king of the world we are living in”.
He said, “Only those who are introduced into this occult are the chosen ones,
so you are the chosen one”.
On the third day which he spoke about, we went back.
In his hand, there was a charm.
In South Africa, we know it as ‘umuti’.
We went into the mountain and he told me that we must bow because
that day I was going to be introduced to the king of the occult
who was going to give me the power to be one of the chosen ones of the occult.
He told me that we must bow and we did.
Then, he started praying in the way of the occult, in the tongues of the occult.
As he was praying he told me that
he had to take a drop of my blood and mix it with the charm,
so that I could throw it in the water.
In that mountain was water.
He said, “I want to throw it in the water and it will call the king of the occult to come out and initiate you”.
He took a drop of my blood, mixed it with the charm and threw it in the water.
As he was making incantations, there was a wind blowing and surrounding us
and then it went back to the water.
I saw the water opening and then something like a monster, half-human and half snake, came out.
He told me, “You don’t have to fear; this is our god, the god of the occult.
He is going to give you the power”.
As he came out physically, I feared.
I wanted to cry but he told me, “Don’t fear”.
I still remember that he repeated it, “Don’t fear. This is your god”.
Then, lucifer came out.
He came out with the body of a snake, crawling.
He came to me but in his hand, he held something.
That elder told me that I must not fear because what he had in his hand,
he was going to give me and I must swallow it.
As he was speaking, he was crawling and coming closer.
Then, he told me to open my mouth.
I opened my mouth and he gave me that thing.
I swallowed it.
As I swallowed it, I felt as if there was a spirit planted in me.
Something just raised up.
He told me that I must not fear, that I must just wait until the god kissed me.
He came closer, kissed my lips and from there, I fainted.
That was how I was initiated.
From there, I woke up at home. I don’t know how I got home.
I woke up there and I wanted to find the elder to explain how I got home.
I went to the place I had found him.
I asked him, "How did I get home?"
I still remember that he told me,
"Son, you don't have to fear and you don’t have to trouble yourself.
Now, you are a full member of this satanic occult".
So, what you are saying here happened physically?
That one happened physically at that mountain in South Africa.
He came with a book and said it was a secret book.
To you Christians, it would seem like a Bible
but it is a bible that is black in colour and red on the sides.
He told me that the book was a secret book for the chosen ones of the cult.
He asked me, "Do you see the colour of this book?"
I said, "Yes, I see".
He said, "On top, the cover is black; do you see it?"
I said, "Yes, I see it".
He said, "It means that all of us born in the world were born into darkness".
I said, "I understand that".
He said, "But we need light and wisdom".
I said, "Yes, I understand that".
He said, "To get into the light to have wisdom, do you see this red colour?"
I said, "Yes, I see it".
He said, "We have to go into the light and get wisdom through the blood".
I said, "I don't understand." He said, "Yes, you won't understand but now,
you will understand because I am teaching you.
Through the blood – not the blood of goats, cows but of human beings -
you will enter the light and then you will have wisdom".
Then he said, "What you ate there in that mountain was a light
that will give you connection to the god in the mountain".
I asked, "How?" He said, "Inside of you, there are two pyramids and an eye.
I said, "Eye?" He said, "Yes".
He said, "This eye in you would make you hear the god in the mountain
when he speaks to you". I asked, "Which god?"
He said, "The one who we all worship; his name is lucifer.
He is our king and he is our leader and we work for him in this earth".
I was shocked.
He told me, "Now, you are the great of the greatest but you must maintain it".
Then, I asked, "How should I maintain it?"
He replied, "Now, you must start fighting that whatever the eye in you,
the spirit, would talk because the eye in you has the spirit".
I remembered because the time in the mountain when I ate that thing,
there was something like a spirit that was planted in me.
From there, I remember that my life was full of destruction -
everything I was doing was hell itself.
Destroying, deceiving and stealing. I was led by the spirit of anger.
We are just listening to our brother who explained his full initiation process.
Brother, we want to go to the area of the assignment that you were given in this satanic cult.
What was your own assignment and how did you go to carry it out in this earth?
I was initiated in 1988. So, in the occult itself, I've got 24 years experience.
In 1996, I was told that there was a special mission that we must do.
I asked myself what the special mission was.
The elder of the occult told me that we must go to the bush
where we would meet our king, lucifer himself.
We went there, met him and they gave us a special mission.
The special mission was to destroy the angel of God in this world, in human body.
I asked who the angel of God was.
They said that the angel of God's mission was to raise the dead churches
and leaders that we, through the power of demons, had destroyed.
In our mission to destroy the churches, we used the power of demons
to deceive many men of God in South Africa to manipulate,
speak badly about Prophet T.B. Joshua.
The angel behind T.B. Joshua himself, they told us that,
that was the angel we must be against and destroy -
destroying him by the power of the demons, spreading lies that he was a liar,
he was part of satanism and that he was not sent by God.
We used many things that they taught us in deceiving people
and many men of God in South Africa through the power of demons.
We used the holy communion in their churches.
First, before we would use the holy communion, we would deceive them.
We captured their minds so that they would allow us to be part of them
and to be part of the departments in their churches.
What we did was, we gained their trust so that they would trust us.
Most of them trusted us because we came to them
as if we were having the power of prophesying.
We came to them offering because most of them,
we knew that they were lacking financially.
So, we were diverting them away from God as their Provider
for them to focus on us as their providers.
We captured their minds, they focused on us and gave us positions
in the departments of their churches.
The departments we rushed to the most were the holy communion department -
that was the most important one and the counselling department.
In the holy communion, we were mixing our blood with the red juice and red wine
so that we would give it to the Christians and by that, they are automatically initiated.
In our churches, we used holy water because we knew that
God is using the blood and water so we faked them; we made our own.
We knew that Christians believe in it and it is working so we faked our own.
We mixed the water with our semen because semen is part of our lives.
We gave it to them and they were initiated.
Most of them, while drinking it, would have dreams.
Some of them would dream of people coming after them, chasing them.
Some of them saw people stabbing them.
Some of them had dreams seeing themselves eating flesh, killing each other.
That was the way we were initiating.
Brother, you mentioned that one of the methods you used was to enter the minds of people
especially men of God, to be spreading rumours, negative things about Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Can you tell us why were you doing this?
What was the purpose of your entering people to spread rumours about Prophet T.B. Joshua?
We were told that he is the right, appointed, anointed Prophet to raise the dead leaders
of the churches and the churches themselves.
So, we were afraid that he was coming to South Africa to raise the churches
that were already under our kingdom.
Mr Lawrence Moala (Deliverance Testimony)
We were afraid that he was going to raise the pastors that were
already under our kingdom knowingly and some unknowingly.
We were afraid that he was coming to bring back that first power of light,
that first power they had in them.
So, we wanted them to be destroyed and be under our kingdom forever.
That was why we spread rumours and lies about him.
Not only that; we were told that we must kill two birds with one stone.
We were not only deceiving and destroying the pastors,
even the members themselves we were destroying, including their children.
We were attacking schools, especially universities.
We gave them these ribbons.
On this ribbon, it is written that,
'I will cut off witchcraft out of your hands (Micah 5:12)'.
So we came in the name of Jesus but we were not of Jesus Christ.
We had many students and gave some of them wallets.
Just by having a wallet that had the face of the dragon, the skull, with you,
you were automatically initiated because
if you take your money and put it in this wallet,
we had prayed for it.
In satanism, your money represents your blood.
Once you put your money in the wallet,
you are initiating yourself into our kingdom.
From there, we got you.
We had signs like the one you saw now.
This sign is the powerful sign in all departments of the satanic occult.
This sign, when we come into churches and show it,
as I saw myself showing it there,
this sign was the power of the eye.
When we show it, it is to attack your mind so that your mind
wouldn't understand what the man of God was teaching.
When we pushed the sign, the power of demons were capturing your mind
bringing the spirit of confusion.
There was this sign; this sign was blocking blessings.
I tried it but it didn't work here; I was here to try it but it didn't work.
This sign was to stop, block the blessings of the Christians.
I tried it here but it failed because of the power of God,
the power of the Anointing Water and the Anointing Stickers and the light on you
because you've got a light that is covering you.
So, as I entered here, the time I was here to destroy the man of God,
I failed because what I saw was amazing.
You mentioned that you were given the mission specifically to try and destroy Prophet T.B. Joshua.
One of the methods you used was to spread rumours.
What other ways did you try to attack?
Did you ever try to come spiritually to The Synagogue Church of All Nations and what happened?
What attempts have you made to destroy this ministry and Prophet T.B. Joshua?
Regarding this ministry, I tried for 17 years because I started in 1996,
when they told us about The SCOAN.
We came here spiritually. First, we sent demons and the demons were captured;
they didn't come back to us and we were asking ourselves what was going on.
We sent them many times through the king who was lucifer, at that time;
because now, my King is Jesus Christ. Hallelujah!
Mr Lawrence Moala (Deliverance Testimony)
We came again to The SCOAN. I still remember, one day, we came spiritually
because we had the power to come out of our bodies.
The demons themselves were going forward; we knew that our coming here was not a story
but it was a fire in the flesh. So, we came here spiritually.
When we came here, we found out that there were spirit beings outside
but we didn't see them as spirit beings, we saw them as lights
because they were closing their wings.
When we came near, the angels started to open their wings.
They opened their wings and their eyes,
they started to give the light and it blinded our spiritual eyes.
We had the power to see in the spirit but it blinded our spiritual eyes
and we had to go back to our bodies.
Another thing that I want to explain to the world is that when we went back to
our bodies; we were not able to enter at that time
because of the power that the angles used to blind our eyes.
When we got back to our bodies, it was difficult
because when you come out of your body, you don't just leave it like that;
you leave the demons called the seraphical camonics.
Those are the big demons in the satanic occult.
When you come out of your body, you do an exchange – they come in,
giving power by the pyramids in you; it is an exchange.
But when you come into the light and your eyes are blinded, you cannot enter
unless the light that has blinded you disappears and then you are
able to come inside again.
I remember one day, we had a meeting
that we'd better attack through the ushers and the helpers.
And we believed that we would be able to defeat them then
because in many churches, we used the helpers, ushers to destroy the churches.
We got most of them in their homes because in their homes,
they were arguing with their parents and the spirit of anger and stubbornness
and the short tempers that they had opened the way for us to enter them.
We thought that when we came to The SCOAN, we would go through them
but we met with fire because when the evil spirits that entered them came here,
the man of God already had a plan -
he prayed for them before they started working.
Mr Lawrence Moala (Deliverance Testimony)
The demons were captured, and we never saw them again.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
We are learning many valuable lessons from our brother
and we understand that he and the kingdom he once belonged to, tried so many ways to come both
physically and spiritually here to The SCOAN in an attempt to destroy Prophet T.B Joshua.
But each attempt they made failed because of the superior power of God
and light of God and operations here.
Our brother also earlier mentioned specifically that he saw power in the items that came from The SCOAN;
the anointing water and the anointing sticker.
Just to build the faith of those present here, can you tell us from the spiritual perspective:
What can you say about the anointing water and anointing sticker that came from this ministry?
The 'spirit water' which was what we called it in the satanic occult
and they trained us that we must be aware of it and not get close to it.
We were told, and we saw it with our spiritual eyes.
You people of God, just see water.
For us, we saw blood – blood that was coming to us in floods of fire.
It is not just blood but blood in floods of fire.
That is why you hear most of the demons, when they come out, calling it fire
because it is blood in fire.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ, for this wonderful deliverance.
Mr Lawrence Moala (Deliverance Testimony)
I've got a lot to say, a lot to share with you children of God because
I believe that God has delivered me not to sit down and hide what is happening.
I am totally delivered by the God of T.B. Joshua,
the right, anointed and appointed Prophet of God.
I believe in Jesus Christ with all of my heart, mind and spirit
and I believe in the Prophet T.B. Joshua with all of my heart, mind and spirit
because I saw him in the spirit and I see him again physically.
Glory be to God! Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time!
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God’s power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV – Changing Lives, Changing Nations and Changing the World.